{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109908524","data":{"timestamp":" 948109908523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" cf6e4c58-241b-40dc-b2a6-9aad0d39428a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anansi alisema moyoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109927350","data":{"timestamp":" 948109927349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109935109","data":{"timestamp":" 948109935108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109937334","data":{"timestamp":" 948109937334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" START_BUIBUI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109939274","data":{"timestamp":" 948109939274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" START_ALIVUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109940985","data":{"timestamp":" 948109940985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109941958","data":{"timestamp":" 948109941958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ALIVUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109945667","data":{"timestamp":" 948109945666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109948581","data":{"timestamp":" 948109948581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUNA"," userResponse":" ALIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109950777","data":{"timestamp":" 948109950776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109951767","data":{"timestamp":" 948109951767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109953441","data":{"timestamp":" 948109953441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUU"," userResponse":" VIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109954107","data":{"timestamp":" 948109954107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109957781","data":{"timestamp":" 948109957781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109958744","data":{"timestamp":" 948109958743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109960446","data":{"timestamp":" 948109960445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109961073","data":{"timestamp":" 948109961073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109962150","data":{"timestamp":" 948109962150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109962865","data":{"timestamp":" 948109962864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109963798","data":{"timestamp":" 948109963796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVUNA"," userResponse":" ALIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109964611","data":{"timestamp":" 948109964610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109965280","data":{"timestamp":" 948109965279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUU"," userResponse":" VIKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109965980","data":{"timestamp":" 948109965979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109966580","data":{"timestamp":" 948109966579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja buibui Anansi alivuna viazi vikuu shambani mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109970933","data":{"timestamp":" 948109970932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIPENDEZA"," userResponse":" VILIPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109972643","data":{"timestamp":" 948109972642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109976231","data":{"timestamp":" 948109976230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" START_KUONEKANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109978577","data":{"timestamp":" 948109978577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109980716","data":{"timestamp":" 948109980716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109984583","data":{"timestamp":" 948109984583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109986990","data":{"timestamp":" 948109986989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIPENDEZA"," userResponse":" VILIPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109987215","data":{"timestamp":" 948109987214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109988214","data":{"timestamp":" 948109988213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONEKANA"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109988956","data":{"timestamp":" 948109988955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109989564","data":{"timestamp":" 948109989563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vilipendeza na kuonekana vitamu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948109998378","data":{"timestamp":" 948109998377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110010824","data":{"timestamp":" 948110010824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110012654","data":{"timestamp":" 948110012653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVICHOMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110016907","data":{"timestamp":" 948110016907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" KUONEKANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110023369","data":{"timestamp":" 948110023369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TARATIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110025624","data":{"timestamp":" 948110025624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110027120","data":{"timestamp":" 948110027120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110027231","data":{"timestamp":" 948110027231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::HF.wrd.len-9.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110059884","data":{"timestamp":" 948110059884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" c0fa18f9-1d19-4949-932d-b7c173354719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alivichoma taratibu kwenye moto na akaanza kula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110080484","data":{"timestamp":" 948110080484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110081195","data":{"timestamp":" 948110081194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110082077","data":{"timestamp":" 948110082076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110082299","data":{"timestamp":" 948110082298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110083211","data":{"timestamp":" 948110083210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110083401","data":{"timestamp":" 948110083400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110083984","data":{"timestamp":" 948110083984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110084615","data":{"timestamp":" 948110084614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110102611","data":{"timestamp":" 948110102611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110105648","data":{"timestamp":" 948110105648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110112754","data":{"timestamp":" 948110112753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110118201","data":{"timestamp":" 948110118201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110121241","data":{"timestamp":" 948110121241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110130913","data":{"timestamp":" 948110130913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110135125","data":{"timestamp":" 948110135124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110137254","data":{"timestamp":" 948110137254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110139152","data":{"timestamp":" 948110139151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110140095","data":{"timestamp":" 948110140095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110140308","data":{"timestamp":" 948110140307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110141081","data":{"timestamp":" 948110141080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110142039","data":{"timestamp":" 948110142039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110142809","data":{"timestamp":" 948110142808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110145922","data":{"timestamp":" 948110145922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110147841","data":{"timestamp":" 948110147840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110149029","data":{"timestamp":" 948110149028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110149710","data":{"timestamp":" 948110149709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110150553","data":{"timestamp":" 948110150553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110154363","data":{"timestamp":" 948110154363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110158158","data":{"timestamp":" 948110158158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110159804","data":{"timestamp":" 948110159803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110160811","data":{"timestamp":" 948110160810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110161629","data":{"timestamp":" 948110161628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" WALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110162417","data":{"timestamp":" 948110162417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110162908","data":{"timestamp":" 948110162907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110163468","data":{"timestamp":" 948110163467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110164583","data":{"timestamp":" 948110164583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110164778","data":{"timestamp":" 948110164778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110165583","data":{"timestamp":" 948110165583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110166603","data":{"timestamp":" 948110166603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MATAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110166835","data":{"timestamp":" 948110166835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110167489","data":{"timestamp":" 948110167489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110168661","data":{"timestamp":" 948110168661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110169662","data":{"timestamp":" 948110169661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110169736","data":{"timestamp":" 948110169736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110170240","data":{"timestamp":" 948110170239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110173429","data":{"timestamp":" 948110173429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110175705","data":{"timestamp":" 948110175705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110178335","data":{"timestamp":" 948110178335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110180203","data":{"timestamp":" 948110180203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110182569","data":{"timestamp":" 948110182569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110185294","data":{"timestamp":" 948110185294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110187637","data":{"timestamp":" 948110187637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110189957","data":{"timestamp":" 948110189957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110209034","data":{"timestamp":" 948110209034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110215492","data":{"timestamp":" 948110215491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110220082","data":{"timestamp":" 948110220082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110221712","data":{"timestamp":" 948110221712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110223374","data":{"timestamp":" 948110223374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110225495","data":{"timestamp":" 948110225494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110227411","data":{"timestamp":" 948110227411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110231248","data":{"timestamp":" 948110231247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110233080","data":{"timestamp":" 948110233080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110234627","data":{"timestamp":" 948110234627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110236571","data":{"timestamp":" 948110236571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110238302","data":{"timestamp":" 948110238301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110239240","data":{"timestamp":" 948110239240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" WALIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110239747","data":{"timestamp":" 948110239747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110240524","data":{"timestamp":" 948110240524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" WAMEBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110241206","data":{"timestamp":" 948110241205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110241435","data":{"timestamp":" 948110241434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110242040","data":{"timestamp":" 948110242040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" MKUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110243315","data":{"timestamp":" 948110243315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" KUWALETEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110243719","data":{"timestamp":" 948110243719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110244243","data":{"timestamp":" 948110244243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110245204","data":{"timestamp":" 948110245204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110245297","data":{"timestamp":" 948110245297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110268933","data":{"timestamp":" 948110268933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" f43c37da-a878-4642-a694-4719db0ee3af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110304408","data":{"timestamp":" 948110304408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 99c00a08-483b-4d22-827a-d624e1ff6e38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110308467","data":{"timestamp":" 948110308467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 99c00a08-483b-4d22-827a-d624e1ff6e38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110338643","data":{"timestamp":" 948110338643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110341427","data":{"timestamp":" 948110341427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110344610","data":{"timestamp":" 948110344610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110348491","data":{"timestamp":" 948110348491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110352201","data":{"timestamp":" 948110352201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110358319","data":{"timestamp":" 948110358319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110365967","data":{"timestamp":" 948110365967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110370282","data":{"timestamp":" 948110370282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110374543","data":{"timestamp":" 948110374543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110378181","data":{"timestamp":" 948110378181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ningekuwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110404104","data":{"timestamp":" 948110404104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110410353","data":{"timestamp":" 948110410353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110413736","data":{"timestamp":" 948110413736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110419579","data":{"timestamp":" 948110419578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110423171","data":{"timestamp":" 948110423171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110429235","data":{"timestamp":" 948110429235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110435602","data":{"timestamp":" 948110435602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110447134","data":{"timestamp":" 948110447134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110451801","data":{"timestamp":" 948110451801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110456874","data":{"timestamp":" 948110456874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110462312","data":{"timestamp":" 948110462312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110475246","data":{"timestamp":" 948110475246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110489988","data":{"timestamp":" 948110489988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110498039","data":{"timestamp":" 948110498039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110501553","data":{"timestamp":" 948110501553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alipoamka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110523016","data":{"timestamp":" 948110523015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110531494","data":{"timestamp":" 948110531494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110535334","data":{"timestamp":" 948110535334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110538959","data":{"timestamp":" 948110538959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110542098","data":{"timestamp":" 948110542098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110548161","data":{"timestamp":" 948110548161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110551453","data":{"timestamp":" 948110551453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110556312","data":{"timestamp":" 948110556312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110560013","data":{"timestamp":" 948110560013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110563604","data":{"timestamp":" 948110563603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110569885","data":{"timestamp":" 948110569885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110585373","data":{"timestamp":" 948110585373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110593511","data":{"timestamp":" 948110593511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuonyesha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110617746","data":{"timestamp":" 948110617746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110620224","data":{"timestamp":" 948110620224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110621813","data":{"timestamp":" 948110621813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110625104","data":{"timestamp":" 948110625104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110630460","data":{"timestamp":" 948110630460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110634539","data":{"timestamp":" 948110634539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110639520","data":{"timestamp":" 948110639520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110643665","data":{"timestamp":" 948110643665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110648826","data":{"timestamp":" 948110648826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_waliongea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110660941","data":{"timestamp":" 948110660941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110663858","data":{"timestamp":" 948110663858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110669518","data":{"timestamp":" 948110669518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110672529","data":{"timestamp":" 948110672529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110678315","data":{"timestamp":" 948110678315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110681578","data":{"timestamp":" 948110681578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110685605","data":{"timestamp":" 948110685605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110692128","data":{"timestamp":" 948110692128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110703929","data":{"timestamp":" 948110703929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110713112","data":{"timestamp":" 948110713112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110717217","data":{"timestamp":" 948110717216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110722112","data":{"timestamp":" 948110722112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110724949","data":{"timestamp":" 948110724949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110730766","data":{"timestamp":" 948110730766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110740199","data":{"timestamp":" 948110740199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110744388","data":{"timestamp":" 948110744388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nilifanya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110801785","data":{"timestamp":" 948110801785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110809504","data":{"timestamp":" 948110809504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110812723","data":{"timestamp":" 948110812722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110816188","data":{"timestamp":" 948110816188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110820870","data":{"timestamp":" 948110820870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110824506","data":{"timestamp":" 948110824506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110833561","data":{"timestamp":" 948110833561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110843326","data":{"timestamp":" 948110843326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110849681","data":{"timestamp":" 948110849681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110852621","data":{"timestamp":" 948110852621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110857856","data":{"timestamp":" 948110857856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110867164","data":{"timestamp":" 948110867164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110879608","data":{"timestamp":" 948110879608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110885779","data":{"timestamp":" 948110885778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110891929","data":{"timestamp":" 948110891929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110902140","data":{"timestamp":" 948110902140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110912301","data":{"timestamp":" 948110912301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mjombangu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110937229","data":{"timestamp":" 948110937229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110942454","data":{"timestamp":" 948110942454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110951090","data":{"timestamp":" 948110951089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110953534","data":{"timestamp":" 948110953534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110955520","data":{"timestamp":" 948110955520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110961070","data":{"timestamp":" 948110961070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110969337","data":{"timestamp":" 948110969337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110979713","data":{"timestamp":" 948110979713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110987528","data":{"timestamp":" 948110987528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110990669","data":{"timestamp":" 948110990669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110994140","data":{"timestamp":" 948110994140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948110998386","data":{"timestamp":" 948110998385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111010253","data":{"timestamp":" 948111010253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111013647","data":{"timestamp":" 948111013647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111017613","data":{"timestamp":" 948111017613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111023399","data":{"timestamp":" 948111023399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alichukua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111045580","data":{"timestamp":" 948111045580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111057097","data":{"timestamp":" 948111057097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111064530","data":{"timestamp":" 948111064530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111073201","data":{"timestamp":" 948111073201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111079955","data":{"timestamp":" 948111079955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111087881","data":{"timestamp":" 948111087880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111099194","data":{"timestamp":" 948111099194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111108192","data":{"timestamp":" 948111108192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111116960","data":{"timestamp":" 948111116960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111120465","data":{"timestamp":" 948111120464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111123096","data":{"timestamp":" 948111123096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111134620","data":{"timestamp":" 948111134620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-9.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111142689","data":{"timestamp":" 948111142688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111175089","data":{"timestamp":" 948111175088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 0d07e06f-cdbd-4c41-8f68-7fd48698d430"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-9.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_unakwenda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111196492","data":{"timestamp":" 948111196492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 14a4d23f-7453-40c0-aafa-097c8b40e9ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111200392","data":{"timestamp":" 948111200391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 14a4d23f-7453-40c0-aafa-097c8b40e9ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948111200469","data":{"timestamp":" 948111200469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000117_145137"," gameId":" 14a4d23f-7453-40c0-aafa-097c8b40e9ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"end":"end"}]}